hai
[music]
and what's up friend I'll call you in 2 minutes what is that I'm doing on the
phone for
online earning today is the due friend I can
pay it today or tomorrow friend it makes a difference
I have to make a lot of calls today it's my
daughter's birthday you must
come in the evening okay friend I'm going out in the evening let's do
one thing let's celebrate your daughter's
birthday tomorrow friend we'll celebrate it on the day it's changed right yes so in the same way
home loan earnings also have to be paid on the due date not
after that otherwise your
name and the money earned over the years will get spoiled
and it will also become difficult to get a loan in the future
understand pay attention to home loan MI on due date
this is the sign of wisdom